youdata.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy - YouData

This policy is effective as of 5/1/2013.

## YouData’s Privacy Policy

YouData’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to provide into your account, and help you make informed decisions when using our MeFileTM service, located at youdata.com and any directly associated domains/sub-domains (collectively, “YouData” or the “Site”).

By using or accessing the Site, you are accepting the practices described in the most current version of our Privacy Policy at that time. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact our privacy staff at info@youdata.com.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

When you register with our Site, you are required to provide only three bits of personal information: your email address, birthdate, and gender. You may optionally (and advisedly) choose to enhance your Mefile with other data points, or "tags", such as various interests, traits, likes, dislikes, and other information that increases the value of your data profile and attracts the most relevant and useful content, ads, and offers. No data is added to your MeFile unless you explicitly place it there yourself.

We do associate IP Addresses with your account and usage of the Site to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer and troubleshoot our Site. We may also use your IP Address or other information about your use of the Site to combat fraudulent activity and to confirm compliance with our User Terms of Service.

### Cookies

When you use our app, we might store small files on your computer called "cookies". Unlike other unseemly varieties of cookies out there, ours do not spy on you, track you, or otherwise invade your privacy. Rather, they are strictly technical devices necessary to help our servers communicate with your personal computing device (PC, tablet, phone, etc.) and to help you navigate and use our application as easily as possible. You may also elect (via the "Remember me" checkbox at Sign In) to use a cookie to prevent you from having to reenter your login credentials at each connection. Please note that this privacy policy covers only the use of cookies by YouData and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers, partners, or other third-party Sites to which we may link outside of our own domain.

### Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on YouData is readily available through your user account. YouData users may modify or delete any of their user account information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated in the live system immediately. Please be aware, that previously edited or deleted data may persist for up to two weeks in our regularly scheduled database backup procedures. Individuals who wish to deactivate their MeFile account may do so on the "Settings" page within their MeFile account. 

### Children Under Age 13

YouData does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the MeFile Service or send any information about yourself to us. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on YouData. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@youdata.com.

### Children From Ages 13 to 17

We recommend that minors from ages 13 to 17 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet, including to YouData.

### Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We do not ever share any of your MeFile data with any third parties, including advertisers and other partners. We consider the data in your MeFile solely your property. It is not ours to share.

### Necessary Use of Third Party Systems

We do use third parties to facilitate and host our business, such as co-location facilities and cloud server providers for database storage, to send out email and other messages, and to process payments among various parties. In connection with these core business operations, our service providers may have access to limited personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the YouData-specified purposes.

### Subpoenas, Court Orders, and Requirements of Law

We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the YouData service or using the YouData name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

### Should YouData Change Ownership

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the YouData business, or individual business units owned by YouData, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

### External Links

Your experience with YouData will likely provide links to other websites and landing pages. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the MeFile service. YouData does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information or MeFile data stored at YouData.

### Security

YouData takes appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. Our Site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. If you have any questions about the security of our Site, please contact us at privacy@youdata.com.

### Terms of Service, Notices and Revisions

Your use of YouData, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this Site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

### Contacting the Site

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@youdata.com](mailto:info@youdata.com).
